We are congressional staffers on Capitol Hill, and we are no longer comfortable being silent.
We were horrified by the brutal October 7th attacks on Israeli civilians, and we are horrified
by the overwhelming response by the Israeli government that has killed thousands of innocent
Palestinian civilians in Gaza.
Our constituents are pleading for a ceasefire, and we are the staffers answering their calls
every day.
Most of our bosses on Capitol Hill are not listening to the people they represent.
We demand our leaders speak up, call for a ceasefire, a release of all hostages, and an
immediate de-escalation now.
We are gathered here today to mourn the loss of every single beautiful and innocent life.
We join now, in a moment of silence, an interfaith prayer for those who we have lost.
We hope we have lost.